<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en_us"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en_us" /><updated>2022-12-15T00:59:00+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">TechWizCo</title><author><name>Sal</name></author><entry><title type="html">Build your own beast plex server</title><link href="/build-your-own-beast-plex-server/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Build your own beast plex server" /><published>2022-12-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/build-your-own-beast-plex-server</id><content type="html" xml:base="/build-your-own-beast-plex-server/"><![CDATA[<p>You can now create your own Beast Plex Server service, which allows users to view and stream their movies, TV episodes, and music in great quality from whatever device they choose. This how-to guide will help you through the process of setting up your own own Plex server.</p>

<h3 id="what-is-a-beast-plex-server">What is a Beast Plex Server?</h3>

<p>All your video, audio, and other visual information is stored, organized, and streamed by the Plex Media Server. Server clients are playback apps that can be installed on a wide range of devices and web browsers.</p>

<p>Plex Media Server is the name of the back-end component, which is free (you do not need to subscribe to a Plex pass account to use it). It can receive content from files, iTunes, iPhoto, Aperture, or the internet and then organize it into a library based on metadata tags like title, artist, album, genre, year, and popularity.</p>

<p>It organizes audio and video content from personal media libraries and streams it to the player, either locally or over a LAN, depending on the user’s preference. Plex works with a variety of operating systems, including Windows, macOS, Linux, and FreeBSD, as well as NAS and the Nvidia Shield TV.</p>

<p>The player apps utilized on the front end include Plex Web App, Plexamp, and Plex Dash. They let the user to manage and play any and all content saved on the Plex Media Server. The great majority of apps are free to download.</p>

<p>Users with free Plex accounts can access Plex, Inc.’s content collection, which includes ad-supported video on demand and free-to-stream live TV channels. These free accounts also enable users to share their personal media libraries with friends or among their own device collection.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/build-your-own-beast-plex-server.avif" alt="Build your own beast plex server" />Source plex.tv</p>

<h3 id="plex-media-server-hardware-requirements">Plex Media Server hardware requirements</h3>

<p>It is critical to adhere to the Plex hardware specifications while building your own beast plex server. Your beast plex server can be run on a desktop computer, server hardware, or a NAS storage device such as Drobo, Netgear, or Synology. A complete Plex NAS compatibility guide <a href="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1MfYoJkiwSqCXg8cm5-Ac4oOLPRtCkgUxU0jdj3tmMPc/edit#gid=1274624273">may be found here</a>.</p>

<h3 id="beast-plex-servers-cpu-requirements">Beast Plex Servers CPU requirements</h3>

<p>The minimum CPU requirements for Plex servers are Intel Core i3, but this is dependent on how many people are accessing content at the same time. Because the server may need transcoding of content during playback at times, you may require something quicker than the minimum.</p>

<p>If your computer’s CPU cannot keep up with transcoding your media, you will notice halting or buffering while the app waits for the server to catch up.</p>

<p>The most important thing to remember is that the more Plex programs that are playing content at the same time, the more processing power is required. When you have two Plex apps operating at the same time, each of which requires transcoded content, the amount of processing power required by your computer’s central processing unit (CPU) nearly doubles when only one program is playing video.</p>

<p>Flex suggests the following CPU specs:</p>

<ul>
  <li>No transcoding: “Atom” 1.2GHz (NAS based on ARM processors)</li>
  <li>Single 720p transcode: Intel i3 3.0 GHz</li>
  <li>Single 1080p transcode: Intel Core i5 3.0GHz</li>
  <li>Single 4K transcode: Intel Core i7 3.2GHz</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="beast-plex-server-memory-requirements">Beast Plex Server memory requirements</h3>

<p>In most cases, Plex Media Server does not need a significant amount of memory (RAM) to provide the service. In most cases, 2 gigabytes of memory is more than adequate. Some installations, particularly those based on Linux, can often run without even that much memory. Having more RAM won’t hurt you in any way, and it will definitely be helpful if you’re using the computer for a variety of tasks at the same time.</p>

<h3 id="is-it-a-good-idea-to-build-your-own-beast-plex-server-on-a-nas">Is it a good idea to build your own beast plex server on a NAS?</h3>

<p>Plex Media Server operating on a network attached storage (NAS) device may be an ideal alternative for some users, but it is not always appropriate for all situations.</p>

<p>The fact that most consumer NAS do not have particularly powerful CPUs is going to be the most aggravating limitation for most customers. In other cases, the mobile device will be powered by an ARM-based processor that lacks any capacity or capabilities for content transcoding.</p>

<p>On other cases, it may run on an Intel processor that is theoretically capable of transcoding but is too slow to transcode at a rate adequate for the majority of applications.</p>

<p>If you want to run your beast plex server on a NAS, you may read a pretty extensive <a href="https://support.plex.tv/articles/201373793-is-plex-media-server-on-a-nas-right-for-me/">article here</a>.</p>

<h3 id="how-to-install-and-build-your-own-beast-plex-server">How to install and build your own beast plex server</h3>

<p>Plex installation is comparable to other software installations, with the exception that you must first install the server software. Once this is completed, you can begin using Plex. Following that, you must install programs on each of your devices in order for them to connect to the server.</p>

<p>Organizing your numerous sources of media is a potentially critical step. As you set up your Plex Material Server, you will begin the process of establishing libraries for your media, such as movies, television shows, music, photographs, and home videos.</p>

<p>Plex will recognize and match material like as movies and TV shows when you do this. It will then collect information such as movie poster artwork, movie casts, and TV episode descriptions, among other things, to beautify your collections.</p>

<h4 id="choosing-a-server-and-performance-considerations">Choosing a server and performance considerations</h4>

<p>Plex Media Server is compatible with computers running Windows, Mac OS X, or Linux; some users run it on their primary computer, while others deploy it on a separate machine. It is also possible to install it on a NAS, provided that it is compatible. In general, Plex runs without any issues on the majority of modern computers.</p>

<p>Keep in mind two important points for providing a good plex media server performance.</p>

<h4 id="media-users">Media Users</h4>

<p>To begin, the Plex Media Server may broadcast material to several users’ devices at the same time. Assume that everyone in your family is watching a film or other sort of media on Plex at the same time, which consumes more server resources. As a result, the server’s power must be increased in proportion to the number of individuals viewing material at the same time.</p>

<h4 id="bandwidth">Bandwidth</h4>

<p>Second, when Plex optimizes your media files for specific devices or available bandwidth, it converts (or “transcodes”) the content while it is playing. This needs a tremendous amount of server resources, but it allows you to access all of your stuff, regardless of size, on all of your devices, regardless of size.</p>

<p>Problems with playback, such as stuttering, buffering, or even failure to play at all, indicate that your server lacks the processing power required for the manner you utilize it.</p>

<p>When this happens, it almost always means that the central processing unit (CPU) is struggling to keep up with the number of users, the amount of transcoding, or both. As a result, you should seriously consider updating your gear. It’s also possible that your hardware is fine, but your connection’s speed is the issue.</p>

<h4 id="download-your-beast-plex-server">Download your beast plex server</h4>

<p>Once you’ve selected where you’ll install the Plex Media Server, go to the <a href="https://plex.tv/downloads/">Plex Downloads website</a> and download the server for your device from there. Make sure you select the correct plex server software for your operating system.</p>

<p>It is critical to ensure that the computer acting as the server has an active internet connection during the installation procedure. The setup wizard will then work properly, and you will be able to create an account as it does so.</p>

<h4 id="download-a-plex-player-app">Download a Plex Player App</h4>

<p>While you’re on the Downloads page, you might wish to install a player app for your device. The browser-based Plex Web App is provided with the server; however, to use it on other devices, you will most likely need to download an app.</p>

<p>The beast plex server apps are available for desktops running Windows and Mac OS, mobile devices running Android and iOS, and connected devices such as Amazon Fire TV, Android TV, Roku, Smart TVs, gaming consoles, and so on.</p>

<h3 id="you-beast-plex-server-installation">You beast plex server installation</h3>

<p>The server is compatible with a wide range of operating systems and platforms. Installation is always performed using an installation package and follows the platform’s regular installation method. When working with NAS, it is critical to follow the manufacturer’s add-on installation instructions.</p>

<h4 id="beast-plex-server-on-windows">Beast Plex Server on Windows</h4>

<p>Download the installer file with an.exe file extension to install your beast plex server on Windows 10 or Windows 11.</p>

<p>Run the installer and proceed with the standard Windows 10 installation procedure. After the installation is complete, click the “Launch” button or use the Start button to launch the Beast plex server.</p>

<p>It is time to perform a beast plex software initial configuration when the server has been activated and displays a System Tray icon (the one at the bottom right of the screen). Simply select “Open Plex…” from the Plex system tray menu.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/beast-plex-servre-initial-configuration.avif" alt="Best Plex Server on Windows" /></p>

<h4 id="beast-plex-server-on-mac-os">Beast Plex Server on Mac OS</h4>

<p>To build your own beast plex server on Mac OS, download the Plex Media Server software .zip file, unzip the file, and drag the beast plex app to your Mac Applications folder.</p>

<p>After launching the media server from the Application folder, you can begin initial server setup by clicking on “Open Plex…” from the “&gt;” icon.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/beast-plex-server-initial-setup-on-mac.avif" alt="Beast Plex Server on Mac" />Source plex.tv</p>

<h4 id="beast-plex-server-on-linux">Beast Plex Server on Linux</h4>

<p>To install the Beast Plex server on Fedora/CentOS download the .rpm package with a current version and run “sudo yum install plexmediaserver-x.xx.x.xxxx.x86_64.rpm”. To proceed with the initial server setup, open a browser on the same server and go to http://localhost:32400/web.</p>

<p>To install Beast server on Ubuntu, download the .deb package and run “sudo dpkg -i plexmediaserver-x.xx.x.xxxx.x86_64.deb”. To set up the server, go to the same URL as shown above for the Fedora installation.</p>

<p>By default, the Beast Media Server runs in the context of the user “plex.” Your media directories and files must allow the plex user to read and execute files in order for plex to work properly.</p>

<h4 id="your-beast-server-on-a-network-attached-storage">Your Beast server on a Network Attached Storage</h4>

<p>Download the installation package for your particular NAS and follow your hardware specific installation instructions to install the server. Go to http://nas.ip.address:32400/web address to configure your server.</p>

<h3 id="to-open-the-streaming-web-app-on-a-different-computer">To open the streaming web app on a different computer</h3>

<h4 id="on-the-same-local-network">On the same local network</h4>

<p>If your other computer is on the same local network as your server, you can simply open a browser window, go to the following address, http://local.server.ip.address:32400/web, and you will be connected to the server.</p>

<h4 id="on-a-different-network">On a different network</h4>

<p>If your client is remote on a different network, you have to go through a slightly more complicated procedure of setting up an SSH tunnel to initially configure your server.</p>

<h5 id="ssh-tunnel-on-mac-os-or-linux">SSH tunnel on Mac OS or Linux</h5>

<p>You are going to use a command line on the terminal to configure the tunnel. So, open your terminal and enter the following command: “ssh -L 8888:127.0.0.1:32400 your.server.ip.address”. Now, in your browser, open the following address “http://127.0.0.1:8888/web” and you will be connected to the server.</p>

<h5 id="ssh-tunnel-on-windows">SSH tunnel on Windows</h5>

<p>If your client and the server both use Windows, they support RDP protocol features, and you can connect using a Remote Desktop session.</p>

<p>However, if your server is based on Mac OS or Linux, you would need to use either the built-in SSH client that support SSH tunneling or a Putty application to configure the tunnel. For Putty connection you have to specify a gateway, which is your.server.ip.address, source port 8888, and your destination 127.0.0.1:32400. After everything is set, you can reach your server via your browser at the address http://127.0.0.1:8888/web.</p>

<h3 id="your-media-collection">Your Media Collection</h3>

<p>Finally, properly structuring your media collection is the most crucial step in offering exceptional multimedia server capabilities.</p>

<p>Your media should have a specified file structure that is distinct for media in their own directories, stand-alone media files, and numerous editions in order for the media server to perform properly.</p>

<p>Please see the <a href="https://support.plex.tv/articles/categories/your-media/">Plex full media organization tutorial</a> for help with naming and arranging your music, TV show, and personal media files, as well as employing subtitles.</p>

<h3 id="in-conclusion">In conclusion</h3>

<p>Adding a Beast Plex server to your home network is a great way to increase the storage capacity of your personal media library while also making streaming content easier than ever.</p>

<p>If you use the official Beast Plex application, you will not have access to additional capabilities such as transcoding and background playback. However, if you build your own Beast Plex server, you will be able to tailor it to match your needs while adhering to any constraints you may have.</p>]]></content><author><name>andre</name></author><category term="How To" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Build Your Own Beast Plex Server to run your own streaming video services. Everything you'll need to set up and run the server.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/plex-main-logo.avif" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/plex-main-logo.avif" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">YouTube MP3</title><link href="/youtube-mp3/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="YouTube MP3" /><published>2022-12-06T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/youtube-mp3</id><content type="html" xml:base="/youtube-mp3/"><![CDATA[<p>The most popular file format right now is the YouTube MP3 format. These files can be created at a number of bit rates, allowing you to strike a balance between file quality and total size. Because of the short file size, it has quickly become the most popular method of sending files over the internet. Because all modern browsers support this format, it is the optimum audio file format for both browsers and other media players.</p>

<p>You want to turn a video you saw into a song, but you don’t know how. We understand. It’s possible that you’d prefer to download a video in audio format so that you may listen to it on your iPod, PC, or smartphone later. Converting YouTube videos to MP3 can be difficult if you don’t have the correct tool.</p>

<p>As a result, we’ve produced a list of our top YouTube to MP3 converter suggestions so you can extract the audio from a YouTube video like a true pro. However, before we get to the list of some of the top YouTube MP3 downloaders, let’s start with the basics.</p>

<h3 id="what-youtube-mp3-converter-does">What YouTube MP3 Converter Does</h3>

<p>A “YouTube to MP3 converter” or an online converter can convert the audio from a YouTube video so that it can be stored in MP3 format and quickly retrieved when needed.</p>

<p>When you utilize a YouTube downloader, you can avoid the need for an active internet connection to listen to your favorite YouTube video. This also makes it much easier to share audio files with others.</p>

<p>You can also convert individual episodes of video podcasts into MP3 audio files, download them, and then publish them to a podcast if you make video podcasts. This will allow you to reach a broader audience and increase the visibility of your work. All at no cost!</p>

<h3 id="how-to-choose-right-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter">How To Choose Right Free Youtube To Mp3 Converter</h3>

<p>Creators and marketers are aware of the value that YouTube possesses. However, a powerful tool is required in order to convert YouTube videos into audio tracks. There is no one tool that can meet the needs of everyone searching for a YouTube downloader. However, there are a few considerations to keep in mind:</p>

<h4 id="youtube-mp3-conversion-options">Youtube MP3 Conversion Options</h4>

<p>MP3 downloaders for YouTube now provide a slew of useful functions. Conduct a needs analysis before selecting a tool with the characteristics you require. Is the program, for example, compatible with several formats, such as MP3, MP4, and WAV, in case you need to convert your YouTube videos to one of those formats?</p>

<p>Can you make changes to the clips before downloading the audio? Some users may need to employ batch processing if they wish to convert YouTube videos to MP3.</p>

<p>On the other hand, some folks may require a simple tool that can perform the conversion successfully. So, decide out what you require and hunt for a downloader that can provide it.</p>

<h4 id="youtube-to-mp3-audio-quality">Youtube To MP3 Audio Quality</h4>

<p><img src="/assets/images/youtube-mp3-audio-quality.avif" alt="MP3 audio quality" />Source fossbytes.com</p>

<p>The finest Youtube to MP3 converters create MP3 files to compensate for any audio loss that occurs during the conversion. JPEG, on the other hand, is a lossless standard for compressing images, whereas MP3 is a lossy format for compressing sound.</p>

<p>When lossy formats are employed, the overall quality of the raw audio that was originally captured is always poorer. You can change this so that you are not aware of the difference. However, doing so will result in a greater file size overall.</p>

<p>When it comes to digital audio, MP3 isn’t as crucial as it once was because new electronic gadgets have so much more storage capacity. And Internet connections have so much more bandwidth. Lossy audio compression is no longer necessary thanks to formats like FLAC, which allow you to save files without sacrificing quality.</p>

<p>Even with codecs that do not lose quality, digital audio will always have some quality loss. Even if the ordinary listener cannot detect. This is due to the fact that digital encoding is constrained in terms of bandwidth and sampling, such as the 44.1 kHz sampling rate used in CDs.</p>

<h4 id="youtube-to-mp3-conversion-speed">Youtube to mp3 conversion speed</h4>

<p>Another critical component is the conversion rate provided by the tool. The YouTube MP3 downloader you choose should be able to swiftly convert YouTube videos to MP3 format. It is vital to remember that spending a large amount of time converting videos may affect overall productivity in the long term. Find a converter that works quickly. A competent tool should be able to accomplish the task in between 30 seconds and 2 minutes, depending on the length of the video.</p>

<h4 id="youtube-to-mp3-converter-supported-formats">Youtube to mp3 converter supported formats</h4>

<p>A Youtube to MP3 converter’s primary job is to convert videos to mp3 files. However, ensure that the converter you use can also convert to other popular file formats.</p>

<p>You should be able to convert not just to mp3, but also to other popular audio and video file formats such as MP4, WAV, OGG, PLAC, AAC, and so on.</p>

<h4 id="desktop-or-browser-based-mp3-converters">Desktop or browser based mp3 converters</h4>

<p>When looking for a free YouTube video to MP3 converter, one of the first things you should consider is the total number of videos you want to convert. If you are just going to do this task once or twice, you might probably consider using an online tool. If you require more advanced capabilities, you should consider downloading a specialized desktop app.</p>

<p>Desktop software will also be faster because the data will not be handled on a remote server. Additionally, some apps can convert multiple YouTube videos to MP3 format at the same time.</p>

<p>Because these apps are so popular, it’s crucial to exercise caution when looking for a YouTube to MP3 converter. Malicious malware is not unusual. We are confident in suggesting the tools in this guide because they have all been well tested.</p>

<h3 id="youtube-to-mp3-converter-safety">Youtube to mp3 converter safety</h3>

<p>There are free YouTube to MP3 converters that are safe to use, but there are also a lot that aren’t. Also, there are converters that you can use without risk, but they come with software you don’t need. Some of these pop-up ads could be harmful or lead to fake websites whose main goal is to steal your personal information.</p>

<p>Because of this, you can’t download a free MP3 converter without first reading reviews online. Some of them come with bloatware that takes up space on your hard drive and CPU bandwidth. All of the ones on our list have been checked and found to be completely safe.</p>

<h3 id="youtube-videos-to-mp3-legalities">Youtube Videos to MP3 Legalities</h3>

<p>Unless you subscribe to Youtube Music Premium or Youtube Premium, converting YouTube to MP3 is a violation of the YouTube terms of service. You may not copy, reproduce, distribute, transmit, broadcast, display, sell, license, or otherwise exploit any content for any other purpose without the prior written approval of Youtube.</p>

<p>Youtube’s terms of service encourage you to watch or listen to its content via the Youtube website or a Youtube app. For example, if you have iOS 16 on your phone, you can keep watching/listening to YouTube videos even if a YouTube app is running in the background.</p>

<p>Using an mp3 converter to convert YouTube to mp3 is comparable to the practice of recording radio music to tape cassettes for personal use in the 1980s and 1990s. Of course, when you use an mp3 converter to convert YouTube to mp3, the procedure is clearly traceable and can be used against you.</p>

<p>If you decide to download YouTube video mp3 files, apply common sense and seek professional legal guidance if necessary.</p>

<h3 id="youtube-video-converters">Youtube video converters</h3>

<h4 id="ytd-video-downloader">YTD Video Downloader</h4>

<p><img src="/assets/images/youtube-mp3-ytd-video-downloader.avif" alt="MP3 YTD Video Downloader" /></p>

<p><a href="https://ytddownloader.com">YTD Video Downloader</a> has earned the trust of millions of people all around the world because it is so simple to use. It is routinely updated to incorporate new technologies as they become available. And it offers a wide range of functionalities from which customers can choose. The YTD Video Downloader’s user interface is easy and clear, making it simple to navigate.</p>

<p>YTD is a powerful video downloader and converter that works with a wide range of operating systems. Because it can swiftly download web videos, the free version should be sufficient for the vast majority of users. If you want to avoid being bothered by commercials and download multiple files at the same time, the premium version is the way to go. You may convert YouTube videos to mp3 files with this software, which is among the best accessible.</p>

<p>The main features are:</p>

<ul>
  <li>Download free videos from 50+ sites</li>
  <li>Convert Most Video Formats: mp3, mp4, wmv, flv, mov, 3gp, avi</li>
  <li>Watch free videos later on other devices: iPad, iPhone, iPod, Samsung Galaxy, HTC, Kindle Fire, Blackberry and many others</li>
  <li>Integrated video player to watch your videos right away</li>
  <li>Free video downloader</li>
  <li>YTD video converter</li>
  <li>Super easy to use and fast</li>
</ul>

<p>It is compatible with Windows XP, Vista, 7, 8, and 10. On January 30, 2020, the latest YouTube converter software version 5.9.15 was released.</p>

<h3 id="yt-saver-youtube-converter">YT Saver Youtube Converter</h3>

<p><img src="/assets/images/youtube-mp3-yt-saver.avif" alt="YT saver" />Source ytsaver.net</p>

<p>If you want to convert YouTube videos to MP3, YT SaverYouTube is one of the best YouTube to MP3 converters.</p>

<p>You may use the <a href="https://ytsaver.net/youtube-downloader/">YT Saver Youtube</a> converter to download MP3 songs and videos from over 10,000 different streaming websites, including YouTube. You may also convert YouTube videos to almost any format, including MP3, MP4, MOV, and AAC, among others. Furthermore, if you want to convert videos in bulk, you can utilize YT Saver, which allows you to store YouTube playlists, channels, and multiple videos at once.</p>

<p>YT Saver is not a YouTube converter online. You may, however, not only download YouTube videos but also work with other famous multimedia sites such as Facebook, Instagram, TikTok, Spotify, and so on. High-quality audio and video files in the following formats are available for download:</p>

<p>The software is available in both free and paid versions and is compatible with Windows 7 or later as well as Mac OS 10.10 or later. The most recent version, 5.3.0, was released on July 12, 2022.</p>

<h3 id="4k-video-downloader">4K Video Downloader</h3>

<p><img src="/assets/images/youtube-mp3-4K-video-downloader.avif" alt="Youtube MP3 4K Download" /></p>

<p>Downloading YouTube videos should not be difficult or time-consuming. And <a href="https://www.4kdownload.com/">4K Video Downloader</a> is a free tool that makes this doable. It is very simple to use, very customizable, ad-free, and does not include any other software.</p>

<p>4K Video Downloader allows you to download videos from a range of sources. These websites include YouTube, Vimeo, Facebook, and DailyMotion. You may also extract audio from a video in 150 different formats, including MP3 files, FLAC, OGG, and M4A.</p>

<p>To download an mp3 file, simply open your browser, copy the URL, and then click the “Paste Link” option in the application. Select the desired output format and quality by choosing “Extract audio” or “Extract MP3” and making your options there. Press the “Extract” button, and 4K Video Downloader will handle the rest.</p>

<p>Although the software is not an online converter, it will recognize advertising and skip downloading them. You can change the download speed to avoid 4K Video Downloader consuming bandwidth. You can also set the software to stop after downloads are complete.</p>

<p>Some 4K Video Downloader features include:</p>

<ul>
  <li>Download Videos from YouTube and Many Other Websites for Free With the help of the 4K Video Downloader, it is now feasible to download high-quality videos, playlists, channels, and subtitles from video-sharing websites such as YouTube, Facebook, and Vimeo, amongst others. With the help of the program, you’ll be able to store all of your preferred movies on your desktop computer or portable media player.</li>
  <li>Download videos from YouTube in a resolution of 4K. Users are able to save video files in 3D format using 4K Video Downloader so that they can watch them at a later time.</li>
  <li>In the event that your Internet connection is unreliable, you have the option of activating the “Smart Mode” feature of the application. This will cause the program to choose all of the settings that are suitable for your computer automatically. Simply copy the URL of the playlist or channel that you wish to save, then click the “Paste URL” button.</li>
  <li>To convert your video into the desirable format all you need to do is to click the convert button.</li>
</ul>

<p>The software is available on the Windows, Mac OS, and Linux platforms.</p>

<h3 id="youtube-mp3-snap-downloader">Youtube MP3 Snap Downloader</h3>

<p><img src="/assets/images/youtube-mp3-snap-downloader.avif" alt="Snap Downloader" /></p>

<p><a href="https://snapdownloader.com/youtube-to-mp3-converter">SnapDownloader</a> is an app that allows you to immediately download videos from nearly 900 different platforms, including YouTube, TikTok, Facebook, and many more. You may also download them in high definition if you like.</p>

<p>Furthermore, it allows you to choose the resolution of the file that you download. Besides to HD, the program allows you to download files in resolutions ranging from 144p to 8K. This allows you to select the size and quality of the file you want to download.</p>

<p>After installing SnapDownloader, run it and travel to the program’s settings by clicking the gear icon in the upper-right area of the screen. Now, navigate to Download Settings in the left sidebar and select a spot on your computer to save the data you downloaded.</p>

<p>You can also tell SnapDownloader to add tags and artwork to your files by checking the appropriate boxes in the same part of the settings menu.</p>

<p>Look for videos that you want to download on YouTube. Return to the SnapDownloader app’s main interface, and then select the Video Downloader option from the menu on the left sidebar.</p>

<p>This will open a new browser where you may search through the millions of videos available for download on YouTube. All you have to do to find what you’re looking for is copy and paste a link into the search field or input a keyword.</p>

<p>Choose a video format and quality. After you’ve found a video, click on it to choose it, and then select the video quality that best meets your needs. You can choose from the various resolutions, which include 1080p HD, 720p HD, 4K Ultra HD, 2K Quad HD, and Standard Definition.</p>

<p>SnapDownloader is the perfect option for you if you want a tool that will allow you to download unlimited YouTube videos of any file size in a speedy, secure, and hassle-free manner. The software can also convert them to the mp3 and mp4 file formats with a single click of the convert button.</p>

<p>Nonetheless, a 24-hour free trial period is insufficient for completely examining any software and deciding whether you want to invest $19.99 to enjoy a lifetime subscription. The free trial provides you with a thorough examination of which aspects of this program you should and should not accept.</p>

<p>You also get a 30-day money-back guarantee, which means that if you are unhappy with your purchase, you can easily request a return within the first 30 days.</p>

<p>When you compare the variety of beneficial features to the low price, you will surely be impressed by the value for money offered by this device.</p>

<h3 id="youtube-to-mp3-converter-by-click">Youtube to MP3 converter By Click</h3>

<p><img src="/assets/images/youtube-mp3-by-click.avif" alt="Youtube By Click Downloader" />Source byclickdownloader.com</p>

<p><a href="https://byclickdownloader.com/youtube-to-mp3.php">By Click Downloader</a> is a simple and effective piece of software for downloading YouTube videos. Although it is not an online YouTube converter, this video downloader supports a wide range of video hosting services.  It includes a YouTube downloader, a YouTube converter, a YouTube downloader in Chrome, a Facebook video downloader, a Vimeo downloader, and a Dailymotion downloader.</p>

<p>By Click Downloader can download files and convert them to a variety of formats such as MP3, MP4, FLV, AVI, WMV, 3GP, WAV, and WEBM. Downloading content in all available qualities, including HD and high audio quality, is workable. If you use the free app, you’ll be able to download a whole YouTube playlist right immediately.</p>

<p>The software is always kept up to date with the most recent YouTube user interface version. By Click Downloader was created from the bottom up to be as simple and easy to use as possible.</p>

<h3 id="convert-youtube-to-mp3-with-any-video-converter">Convert Youtube to MP3 with Any Video Converter</h3>

<p><img src="/assets/images/youtube-mp3-any-video-converter.avif" alt="Any Video Converter" />Source byclickdownloader.com</p>

<p>Because <a href="https://www.any-video-converter.com/en6/for_video_free/">Any Video Converter Free</a> is so feature-rich and thorough, it’s difficult to believe it’s free. You may use this free YouTube to MP3 converter to extract files from CDs, download them from YouTube, Vimeo, Facebook, Dailymotion, and other websites. You can apply filters and effects to them, and then save them to your computer or burn them to DVD in nearly any format.</p>

<p>With the help of Any Video Converter Free’s vast collection of capabilities, which are presented in a simple and elegant interface, you will be downloading and converting clips in a matter of seconds. Select an input choice (disk, file, or URL) and the clip to convert. Then select an output device and format before pressing the Convert button. This will conduct a basic conversion for you. The array of output possibilities is astounding, and it covers both audio and video format options.</p>]]></content><author><name>andre</name></author><category term="Reviews" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are YouTube MP3 files, how can you obtain and convert them, and which free YouTube MP3 converters should you use for the best results?]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/youtube-mp3.avif" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/youtube-mp3.avif" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Test Page</title><link href="/test-page/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Test Page" /><published>2022-12-04T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/test-page</id><content type="html" xml:base="/test-page/"><![CDATA[<p>This is a page test to get a feel of the Markdown languages.</p>

<p>This is a second paragraph of the text.</p>

<h1 id="this-is-an-h1-header">This is an H1 header</h1>

<h2 id="this-is-a-h2-header">This is a H2 header</h2>

<h3 id="this-is-an-h3-header">This is an H3 header</h3>

<h4 id="this-is-a-h4-header">This is a H4 header</h4>

<blockquote>
  <p>This is a block quote</p>

  <p>This is a second paragraph in the blockquote</p>

  <h2 id="this-is-h2-in-the-block-quote">This is H2 in the block quote</h2>
</blockquote>

<p>To <strong>emphasize</strong> some words.</p>

<p>This is a list</p>
<ul>
  <li>one</li>
  <li>two</li>
  <li>three</li>
</ul>

<p>This is a numbered list</p>
<ol>
  <li>one</li>
  <li>two</li>
  <li>three</li>
</ol>

<p>I get 10 times more traffic from <a href="https://google.com" title="Google">Google</a> than from
<a href="https://search.yahoo.com/" title="Yahoo Search">Yahoo</a> or <a href="https://msn.com]" title="MSN Search">MSN</a>.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/2.jpg" alt="TEST TEXT" title="This is Title" /></p>

<p>Horizontal rule tag</p>
<hr />

<p><code>This is a python code
python3 -v</code></p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/2.jpg" alt="alt text" title="Logo Title Text 2" /></p>

<p>Colons can be used to align columns.</p>

<table>
  <thead>
    <tr>
      <th>Tables</th>
      <th style="text-align: center">Are</th>
      <th style="text-align: right">Cool</th>
    </tr>
  </thead>
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <td>col 3 is</td>
      <td style="text-align: center">right-aligned</td>
      <td style="text-align: right">$1600</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>col 2 is</td>
      <td style="text-align: center">centered</td>
      <td style="text-align: right">$12</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>zebra stripes</td>
      <td style="text-align: center">are neat</td>
      <td style="text-align: right">$1</td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>

<table>
  <thead>
    <tr>
      <th>Markdown</th>
      <th>Less</th>
      <th>Pretty</th>
    </tr>
  </thead>
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <td><em>Still</em></td>
      <td><code>renders</code></td>
      <td><strong>nicely</strong></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>1</td>
      <td>2</td>
      <td>3</td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>

<p>Another attempt</p>

<table>
  <thead>
    <tr>
      <th style="text-align: left">Syntax</th>
      <th style="text-align: center">Description</th>
      <th style="text-align: right">Test Text</th>
    </tr>
  </thead>
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <td style="text-align: left">Header</td>
      <td style="text-align: center">Title</td>
      <td style="text-align: right">Here’s this</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td style="text-align: left">Paragraph</td>
      <td style="text-align: center">Text</td>
      <td style="text-align: right">And more</td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>

<p><del>The world is flat.</del> We now know that the world is round.</p>

<ul class="task-list">
  <li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" disabled="disabled" checked="checked" />Write the press release</li>
  <li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" disabled="disabled" />Update the website</li>
  <li class="task-list-item"><input type="checkbox" class="task-list-item-checkbox" disabled="disabled" />Contact the media</li>
</ul>

<p>Dillinger uses a number of open source projects to work properly:</p>

<ul>
  <li>[AngularJS] - HTML enhanced for web apps!</li>
  <li>[Ace Editor] - awesome web-based text editor</li>
  <li>[markdown-it] - Markdown parser done right. Fast and easy to extend.</li>
  <li>[Twitter Bootstrap] - great UI boilerplate for modern web apps</li>
  <li>[node.js] - evented I/O for the backend</li>
  <li>[Express] - fast node.js network app framework [@tjholowaychuk]</li>
  <li>[Gulp] - the streaming build system</li>
  <li><a href="https://breakdance.github.io/breakdance/">Breakdance</a> - HTML
to Markdown converter</li>
  <li>[jQuery] - duh</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>andy</name></author><category term="Reviews" /><category term="tutorial" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a page test to get a feel of the Markdown languages.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/3.avif" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/3.avif" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Powerful things you can do with the Markdown editor</title><link href="/powerful-things-markdown-editor/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Powerful things you can do with the Markdown editor" /><published>2020-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/powerful-things-markdown-editor</id><content type="html" xml:base="/powerful-things-markdown-editor/"><![CDATA[<p>There are lots of powerful things you can do with the Markdown editor</p>

<p>If you’ve gotten pretty comfortable with writing in Markdown, then you may enjoy some more advanced tips about the types of things you can do with Markdown!</p>

<p>As with the last post about the editor, you’ll want to be actually editing this post as you read it so that you can see all the Markdown code we’re using.</p>

<h2 id="special-formatting">Special formatting</h2>

<p>As well as bold and italics, you can also use some other special formatting in Markdown when the need arises, for example:</p>

<ul>
  <li><del>strike through</del></li>
  <li>==highlight==</li>
  <li>*escaped characters*</li>
</ul>

<h2 id="writing-code-blocks">Writing code blocks</h2>

<p>There are two types of code elements which can be inserted in Markdown, the first is inline, and the other is block. Inline code is formatted by wrapping any word or words in back-ticks, <code>like this</code>. Larger snippets of code can be displayed across multiple lines using triple back ticks:</p>

<pre><code>.my-link {
    text-decoration: underline;
}
</code></pre>

<p>If you want to get really fancy, you can even add syntax highlighting using Rouge.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/3.jpg" alt="walking" /></p>

<h2 id="reference-lists">Reference lists</h2>

<p>The quick brown jumped over the lazy.</p>

<p>Another way to insert links in markdown is using reference lists. You might want to use this style of linking to cite reference material in a Wikipedia-style. All of the links are listed at the end of the document, so you can maintain full separation between content and its source or reference.</p>

<h2 id="full-html">Full HTML</h2>

<p>Perhaps the best part of Markdown is that you’re never limited to just Markdown. You can write HTML directly in the Markdown editor and it will just work as HTML usually does. No limits! Here’s a standard YouTube embed code as an example:</p>

<p><iframe style="width:100%;" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Cniqsc9QfDo?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p>]]></content><author><name>sal</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><category term="tutorial" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are lots of powerful things you can do with the Markdown editor]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/4.avif" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/4.avif" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">We all wait for summer</title><link href="/we-all-wait-for-summer/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="We all wait for summer" /><published>2020-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/we-all-wait-for-summer</id><content type="html" xml:base="/we-all-wait-for-summer/"><![CDATA[<p>This is changed. As I engage in the so-called “bull sessions” around and about the school, I too often find that most college men have a misconception of the purpose of education. Most of the “brethren” think that <a href="#">education should equip</a> them with the proper instruments of exploitation so that they can forever trample over the masses. Still others think that education should furnish them with noble ends rather than means to an end.</p>

<p>It seems to me that education has a two-fold function to perform in the life of man and in society: the one is utility and the other is culture. Education must enable a man to become more efficient, to achieve with increasing facility the ligitimate goals of his life.</p>]]></content><author><name>Sal</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><category term="tutorial" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is changed. As I engage in the so-called “bull sessions” around and about the school, I too often find that most college men have a misconception of the purpose of education. Most of the “brethren” think that education should equip them with the proper instruments of exploitation so that they can forever trample over the masses. Still others think that education should furnish them with noble ends rather than means to an end.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/1.avif" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/1.avif" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Green Riding Hood</title><link href="/red-riding/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Green Riding Hood" /><published>2020-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/red-riding</id><content type="html" xml:base="/red-riding/"><![CDATA[<p>The first mass-produced book to deviate from a rectilinear format, at least in the United States, is thought to be this 1863 edition of Red Riding Hood, cut into the shape of the protagonist herself with the troublesome wolf curled at her feet. Produced by the Boston-based publisher Louis Prang, this is the first in their “Doll Series”, a set of five “die-cut” books, known also as shape books — the other titles being Robinson Crusoe, Goody Two-Shoes (also written by Red Riding Hood author Lydia Very), Cinderella, and King Winter.</p>

<p>An 1868 Prang catalogue would later claim that such “books in the shape of a regular paper Doll… originated with us”.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>It would seem the claim could also extend to die cut books in general, as we can’t find anything sooner, but do let us know in the comments if you have further light to shed on this! Such books are, of course, still popular in children’s publishing today, though the die cutting is not now limited to mere outlines, as evidenced in a beautiful 2014 version of the same Little Red Riding Hood story.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>The die cut has also been employed in the non-juvenile sphere as well, a recent example being Jonathan Safran Foer’s ambitious Tree of Codes.</p>

<p>As for this particular rendition of Charles Perrault’s classic tale, the text and design is by Lydia Very (1823-1901), sister of Transcendentalist poet Jones Very. The gruesome ending of the original — which sees Little Red Riding Hood being gobbled up as well as her grandmother — is avoided here, the gore giving way to the less bloody aims of the morality tale, and the lesson that one should not disobey one’s mother.</p>]]></content><author><name>sal</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><category term="tutorial" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first mass-produced book to deviate from a rectilinear format, at least in the United States, is thought to be this 1863 edition of Red Riding Hood, cut into the shape of the protagonist herself with the troublesome wolf curled at her feet. Produced by the Boston-based publisher Louis Prang, this is the first in their “Doll Series”, a set of five “die-cut” books, known also as shape books — the other titles being Robinson Crusoe, Goody Two-Shoes (also written by Red Riding Hood author Lydia Very), Cinderella, and King Winter.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/3.avif" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/3.avif" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Markdown Example</title><link href="/markup-example/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Markdown Example" /><published>2020-01-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/markup-example</id><content type="html" xml:base="/markup-example/"><![CDATA[<p>You’ll find this post in your <code>_posts</code> directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run <code>jekyll serve</code>, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated. Something.</p>

<p>To add new posts, simply add a file in the <code>_posts</code> directory that follows the convention <code>YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext</code> and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.</p>

<p>Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:</p>

<figure class="highlight"><pre><code class="language-ruby" data-lang="ruby"><span class="k">def</span> <span class="nf">print_hi</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="nb">name</span><span class="p">)</span>
  <span class="nb">puts</span> <span class="s2">"Hi, </span><span class="si">#{</span><span class="nb">name</span><span class="si">}</span><span class="s2">"</span>
<span class="k">end</span>
<span class="n">print_hi</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="s1">'Tom'</span><span class="p">)</span>
<span class="c1">#=&gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.</span></code></pre></figure>

<p>Check out the <a href="http://jekyllrb.com/docs/home">Jekyll docs</a> for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at <a href="https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll">Jekyll’s GitHub repo</a>. If you have questions, you can ask them on <a href="https://talk.jekyllrb.com/">Jekyll Talk</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name>john</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><category term="tutorial" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated. Something.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/6.avif" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/6.avif" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Is Intelligence Enough</title><link href="/is-intelligence-enough/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Is Intelligence Enough" /><published>2019-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/is-intelligence-enough</id><content type="html" xml:base="/is-intelligence-enough/"><![CDATA[<p>Education must also train one for quick, resolute and effective thinking. To think incisively and to think for one’s self is very difficult.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>We are prone to let our mental life become invaded by legions of half truths, prejudices, and propaganda. At this point, I often wonder whether or not education is fulfilling its purpose. A great majority of the so-called educated people do not think logically and scientifically.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Even the press, the classroom, the platform, and the pulpit in many instances do not give us objective and unbiased truths. To save man from the morass of propaganda, in my opinion, is one of the chief aims of education. Education must enable one to sift and weigh evidence, to discern the true from the false, the real from the unreal, and the facts from the fiction.</p>

<p>The function of education, therefore, is to teach one to think intensively and to think critically. But education which stops with efficiency may prove the greatest menace to society. The most dangerous criminal may be the man gifted with reason, but with no morals.</p>

<p>The late Eugene Talmadge, in my opinion, possessed one of the better minds of Georgia, or even America. Moreover, he wore the Phi Beta Kappa key. By all measuring rods, Mr. Talmadge could think critically and intensively; yet he contends that I am an inferior being. Are those the types of men we call educated?</p>

<p>We must remember that intelligence is not enough. Intelligence plus character–that is the goal of true education. The complete education gives one not only power of concentration, but worthy objectives upon which to concentrate. The broad education will, therefore, transmit to one not only the accumulated knowledge of the race but also the accumulated experience of social living.</p>]]></content><author><name>sal</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><category term="tutorial" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Education must also train one for quick, resolute and effective thinking. To think incisively and to think for one’s self is very difficult.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/5.avif" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/5.avif" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Tree of Codes</title><link href="/tree-of-codes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tree of Codes" /><published>2018-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/tree-of-codes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/tree-of-codes/"><![CDATA[<p>The first mass-produced book to deviate from a rectilinear format, at least in the United States, is thought to be this 1863 edition of Red Riding Hood, cut into the shape of the protagonist herself with the troublesome wolf curled at her feet. Produced by the Boston-based publisher Louis Prang, this is the first in their “Doll Series”, a set of five “die-cut” books, known also as shape books — the other titles being Robinson Crusoe, Goody Two-Shoes (also written by Red Riding Hood author Lydia Very), Cinderella, and King Winter.</p>

<p>As for this particular rendition of Charles Perrault’s classic tale, the text and design is by Lydia Very (1823-1901), sister of Transcendentalist poet Jones Very. The gruesome ending of the original — which sees Little Red Riding Hood being gobbled up as well as her grandmother — is avoided here, the gore giving way to the less bloody aims of the morality tale, and the lesson that one should not disobey one’s mother.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>It would seem the claim could also extend to die cut books in general, as we can’t find anything sooner, but do let us know in the comments if you have further light to shed on this! Such books are, of course, still popular in children’s publishing today, though the die cutting is not now limited to mere outlines, as evidenced in a beautiful 2014 version of the same Little Red Riding Hood story.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>An 1868 Prang catalogue would later claim that such “books in the shape of a regular paper Doll… originated with us”.</p>

<p>The die cut has also been employed in the non-juvenile sphere as well, a recent example being Jonathan Safran Foer’s ambitious Tree of Codes.</p>]]></content><author><name>sal</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><category term="tutorial" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first mass-produced book to deviate from a rectilinear format, at least in the United States, is thought to be this 1863 edition of Red Riding Hood, cut into the shape of the protagonist herself with the troublesome wolf curled at her feet. Produced by the Boston-based publisher Louis Prang, this is the first in their “Doll Series”, a set of five “die-cut” books, known also as shape books — the other titles being Robinson Crusoe, Goody Two-Shoes (also written by Red Riding Hood author Lydia Very), Cinderella, and King Winter.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/2.avif" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/2.avif" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>